Casey Lin: Okay, let's do this. Sprint review for the pricing page.
Casey Lin: Quick agenda — Mia walks us through final hi-fi, Wes and Devon update on the engineering side, then we lock what's actually shipping Friday.
Mia Torres: Sounds good. I'll share my screen — give me one second.
Mia Torres: Right. So this is where we landed. Three pricing tiers across the top — Starter, Pro, and Scale. The big change from last week is the comparison table. I tried two versions and honestly neither felt right at this card density.
Devon Park: Yeah, I built the prototype for that table on Monday and it adds about eighty kilobytes to the page.
Wes Chen: And it doesn't render well on mobile under three-fifty pixels wide. We'd have to redesign the breakpoint.
Casey Lin: Okay, that's a real trade-off. Mia, what would you cut to make it ship?
Mia Torres: I'd cut the comparison table from this sprint and keep just the three tier cards. That's what most of the inbound is responding to anyway based on the May test.
Casey Lin: I'm fine with that. Anyone disagree? Going once.
Devon Park: No, it's the right call. Comparison table can be its own ticket next sprint.
Casey Lin: Decision then — we ship without the comparison table this sprint. Mia, will you file the follow-up ticket?
Mia Torres: Yep, I'll write it up after this meeting.
Casey Lin: Second thing — the tier names. Pro is doing weird things in user testing. People assume it's the cheapest paid tier.
Mia Torres: I noticed that too. I think we should just call it Team. It maps to what they actually buy.
Wes Chen: Are we changing the underlying SKU IDs? Because that's a Stripe migration if so.
Mia Torres: No — display name only. The internal SKU stays plan_pro. So no Stripe work.
Casey Lin: Okay then let's do it. Pro becomes Team in the UI. Mia, that goes in the same hi-fi update?
Mia Torres: Yes. Tuesday EOD.
Casey Lin: Wes, what's the engineering picture? When can the page actually go behind the flag?
Wes Chen: I need Mia's final hi-fi by Tuesday end of day to wire it up. Stripe checkout link is a one-day swap once she lands. So I can have it behind the flag by Wednesday end of day, ready for QA Thursday.
Devon Park: I'll add the analytics tracking by Thursday morning. We'll need the conversion events defined before then though — I haven't gotten that spec.
Casey Lin: That's on me. I'll send you the event list by Tuesday morning.
Devon Park: Great. Then yeah, Thursday for tracking, Friday morning for QA cycle, ship Friday afternoon if no surprises.
Casey Lin: Quick question — should we A/B-test the prices? I keep going back and forth on this.
Mia Torres: I think we should hold off. We don't have enough traffic on the pricing page to get a clean read in under three weeks, and we're going to keep iterating anyway.
Wes Chen: Plus the experiment infrastructure for pricing tiers is a whole project itself.
Casey Lin: Fair. Let's defer A/B and just ship. We can revisit in Q2.
Devon Park: One concern — mobile QA. Mia, are we doing real device testing or just Chrome devtools?
Mia Torres: I'd really want at least an iPhone 12 and a mid-tier Android in front of someone before we ship. The new card layout has some Safari-specific quirks I caught last week.
Casey Lin: Okay — Wes, can you book thirty minutes Friday morning with someone in IT to grab the test devices?
Wes Chen: I'll set it up. Adding it to my Friday now.
Casey Lin: Risks I want to surface for the wider team — biggest one is that we're shipping without the comparison table, so sales might push back.
Mia Torres: I can write a note in the launch doc explaining why and what's coming next sprint. That'll cut down on the back-and-forth.
Casey Lin: Perfect. Add that to your Tuesday list.
Casey Lin: Last thing — how are we measuring success post-launch? I want this defined before we hit publish.
Devon Park: I'd propose two numbers — start-trial conversion rate from the pricing page, and Team-tier share of new signups. Baseline against the last 30 days.
Casey Lin: That works. Devon, can you build a small dashboard so we're not chasing this in Mixpanel every Monday?
Devon Park: Yep. I'll have it up by the end of next week. Lower priority than the launch itself.
Casey Lin: Anything else? Anyone blocked or sandbagging?
Wes Chen: Nope. Tuesday hi-fi, Wednesday flag, Thursday tracking, Friday QA, Friday ship.
Mia Torres: Same. I have everything I need to land Tuesday.
Casey Lin: All right. Talk Wednesday standup.